[Music]
your real talk I wrote this shit like an
hour nice hotel room follow me on
instagram at george hotz curtains closed
this is closest to get to the cloud if i
was trying to touch i'm gonna be too
look at me now but there's a little
hitch a certain feels a downpour meow
let me tell you when it all went south
you see I used to be the guy to follow
in my trucks and go north get in my car
and drive we move it's fine and never be
caught into a normal life and never good
to fucks but what you thought was right
flip our bosses are rollin heel is buy
and make our choices daily if we want a
trial a tour today in the for tonight
and just drive the mania way for the
rest of our life but I was smoking weed
when I got caught up with some plans
just to brag that I only thought a week
in advance it was a Midsummer's Night I
didn't see the demands I was hungry it
slipped and saw my soul to the man when
you sell to the devil the deal is never
straightforward its honest on paper but
you see the consequence later you can
scream it's the world but that shit
doesn't help the best you can do is
fucking screaming yourself you stupid
bitch how could you do me like this we
used to be free now we're doing emails
and shit you say you don't have a boss
but you're acting so whipped okay I fell
for the scam and molix a dick